{
    "childName": "hasam",
    "dob": "2024-10-22",
    "picture": null,
    "gender": "female",
    "questions": [
        {
            "answer": [
                "Drawing/Painting",
                "Sports/Running",
                "Video Games",
                "Exploring Nature",
                "Playing"
            ],
            "question": " What are some hobbies or activities they really enjoy?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "value": 1,
                    "label": "🧑‍🎨 Drawing/Painting"
                },
                {
                    "value": 2,
                    "label": "🏃 Sports/Running"
                },
                {
                    "value": 3,
                    "label": "🎮 Video Games"
                },
                {
                    "value": 4,
                    "label": "🧩 Solving Puzzles"
                },
                {
                    "value": 5,
                    "label": "🎸 Playing"
                },
                {
                    "value": 6,
                    "label": "🌳 Exploring Nature"
                },
                {
                    "value": 7,
                    "label": "🏰 Building (Legos, Blocks)"
                },
                {
                    "value": 8,
                    "label": "🎤 Singing/Dancing"
                },
                {
                    "value": 9,
                    "label": "🧑‍🍳 Cooking"
                },
                {
                    "value": 10,
                    "label": "📖 Reading Books"
                },
                {
                    "value": 11,
                    "label": "📝 Other"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "answer": [
                "Reading Club",
                "Robotics/Coding Club",
                "Puzzle/Chess Club",
                "Science Club"
            ],
            "question": "Do they attend any clubs or classes regularly?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "value": 1,
                    "label": "🎨 Art Class"
                },
                {
                    "value": 2,
                    "label": "🏀 Sports Team"
                },
                {
                    "value": 3,
                    "label": "🎶 Music Class"
                },
                {
                    "value": 4,
                    "label": "🤖 Robotics/Coding Club"
                },
                {
                    "value": 5,
                    "label": "📚 Reading Club"
                },
                {
                    "value": 6,
                    "label": "🧩 Puzzle/Chess Club"
                },
                {
                    "value": 7,
                    "label": "🏊 Swimming Class"
                },
                {
                    "value": 8,
                    "label": "🎭 Drama/Theater Group"
                },
                {
                    "value": 9,
                    "label": "🧑‍🔬 Science Club"
                },
                {
                    "value": 10,
                    "label": "💃 Dance Class"
                },
                {
                    "value": 11,
                    "label": "📝 Other"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "answer": "fffdfdfd",
            "question": "Do they attend any clubs or classes regularly?",
            "options": null,
            "inputtext": true
        },
        {
            "answer": "fdfdfdfd",
            "question": "Do they attend any clubs or classes regularly?",
            "options": null,
            "inputtext": true
        },
        {
            "answer": [
                "Basketball",
                "Volleyball"
            ],
            "question": "Are they involved in any sports regularly?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "value": 1,
                    "label": "⚽ Soccer"
                },
                {
                    "value": 2,
                    "label": "🏀 Basketball"
                },
                {
                    "value": 3,
                    "label": "🏊 Swimming"
                },
                {
                    "value": 4,
                    "label": "🏸 Badminton"
                },
                {
                    "value": 5,
                    "label": "🏃 Running"
                },
                {
                    "value": 6,
                    "label": "🏐 Volleyball"
                },
                {
                    "value": 7,
                    "label": "🎾 Tennis"
                },
                {
                    "value": 8,
                    "label": "🥋 Martial Arts"
                },
                {
                    "value": 9,
                    "label": "🏋️ Gymnastics"
                },
                {
                    "value": 10,
                    "label": "🚴 Cycling"
                },
                {
                    "value": 11,
                    "label": "📝 Other"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "answer": [
                "Making Costumes"
            ],
            "question": " What are some hobbies or activities they really enjoy?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "value": 1,
                    "label": "🎨 Painting"
                },
                {
                    "value": 2,
                    "label": "✂️ Crafting"
                },
                {
                    "value": 3,
                    "label": "🧶 Knitting/Sewing"
                },
                {
                    "value": 4,
                    "label": "🧵 Making Jewelry"
                },
                {
                    "value": 5,
                    "label": "🖌 Sculpting"
                },
                {
                    "value": 6,
                    "label": "🧩 DIY Projects"
                },
                {
                    "value": 7,
                    "label": "📒 Scrapbooking"
                },
                {
                    "value": 8,
                    "label": "🎭 Making Costumes"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "answer": "dffdfd",
            "question": " What are some hobbies or activities they really enjoy?",
            "options": null,
            "inputtext": true
        },
        {
            "answer": "fdfdfd",
            "question": " What are some hobbies or activities they really enjoy?",
            "options": null,
            "inputtext": true
        },
        {
            "answer": "dfdfdffd",
            "question": " What are some hobbies or activities they really enjoy?",
            "options": null,
            "inputtext": true
        },
        {
            "answer": "dffddffd",
            "question": " What are some hobbies or activities they really enjoy?",
            "options": null,
            "inputtext": true
        },
        {
            "answer": [
                "Kids/Family",
                "Musicals"
            ],
            "question": "Do they like watching movies? What genres do they enjoy?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "value": 1,
                    "label": "🎬 Action/Adventure"
                },
                {
                    "value": 2,
                    "label": "🦸 Superhero Movies"
                },
                {
                    "value": 3,
                    "label": "😂 Comedy"
                },
                {
                    "value": 4,
                    "label": "🧙 Fantasy"
                },
                {
                    "value": 5,
                    "label": "👻 Horror"
                },
                {
                    "value": 6,
                    "label": "🕵️ Mystery/Thriller"
                },
                {
                    "value": 7,
                    "label": "🌍 Documentary"
                },
                {
                    "value": 8,
                    "label": "💖 Romantic"
                },
                {
                    "value": 9,
                    "label": "🐉 Animated"
                },
                {
                    "value": 10,
                    "label": "👑 Historical/Period Drama"
                },
                {
                    "value": 11,
                    "label": "🏰 Fairy Tales"
                },
                {
                    "value": 12,
                    "label": "🚀 Sci-Fi"
                },
                {
                    "value": 13,
                    "label": "🎵 Musicals"
                },
                {
                    "value": 14,
                    "label": "🤖 Supernatural/Sci-Fi Fantasy"
                },
                {
                    "value": 15,
                    "label": "👶 Kids/Family"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}